[Jason Snider](https://jasonsnider.com/)Menu

Privacy Policy
==============

Your privacy is important to us. It is Jason Snider's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, [http://jasonsnider.com](http://jasonsnider.com/), and other sites we own and operate.

We only ask for personal information when we truly need it to provide a service to you. We collect it by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will be used.

We only retain collected information for as long as necessary to provide you with your requested service. What data we store, we’ll protect within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.

Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and practices of these sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy policies.

You are free to refuse our request for your personal information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services.

Your continued use of our website will be regarded as acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information. If you have any questions about how we handle user data and personal information, feel free to contact us.

Third-Party Services
--------------------

In general, third-party services should only collect, use, and disclose your information at the lowest required level. Please read the privacy policies of all the third-party services listed on this page. I am not responsible for the practices or misdeeds of third party services.

### Formspree

I use Formspree on my concat page ([Formspree privacy policy](https://formspree.io/static/PrivacyPolicy.pdf)).

This policy is subject to change without notice, this policy and all changes are to be considered effective as of the modified date below.

_Posted: 2018-10-19 01:34:11_

_Modified: 2018-10-22 01:27:36_

Built withloveby Jason in Chicago
